So how does sending HTTP requests work in react applications typically
W jaki sposb wysyanie da HTTP dziaa zazwyczaj w reakcji na aplikacje
and I'm saying typically because if you're creating a multi-page react application, there actually isn't
i zazwyczaj mwi, poniewa jeli tworzysz aplikacj obsugujc wiele stron, nie ma w
anything special to it.
niej nic szczeglnego.
You probably have your application, your page where you submit a form and that sends a request to your
Prawdopodobnie masz aplikacj, stron, na ktrej przesyasz formularz, i ktry wysya danie do twojego
backend and you get back a new html page with potentially new react code in there.
backendu, a ty otrzymujesz z powrotem now stron html z potencjalnie nowym kodem reakcji.
You don't have a single page application,
Nie masz aplikacji na jedn
you don't have a strong decoupling going on.
stron, nie masz silnego oddzielenia.
If you have such a single page application, you have a strong differentiation between your frontend,
Jeli masz tak aplikacj na jedn stron, masz due zrnicowanie
your react app and your backend though. The react app and the servers still need to communicate from time
midzy aplikacj, aplikacj i backendem. Reakcja aplikacji i serwerw wci wymagaj komunikacji
to time but they don't communicate by exchanging html pages.
od czasu do czasu, ale nie komunikuj si poprzez wymian stron html.
So if a react app sends a request to a server,
Jeli wic aplikacja reagujca wyle danie na
you don't get back a new html page instead you can back some json data typically or you send
serwer, nie otrzymasz nowej strony html, zamiast tego moesz zazwyczaj przywrci niektre dane json lub przesa niektre dane
some json data to the server
json do serwera, jeli chcesz
if you want to create some resources on the server for example. This is how that works, you have that
utworzy pewne zasoby na serwerze dla przykad. Tak to dziaa, masz to oddzielenie,
decoupling and your server
a twj serwer to zazwyczaj
therefore typically is a RESTful API, just exposing some API endpoints to which you can send requests
RESTful API, po prostu ujawniajcy niektre punkty kocowe API, do ktrych moesz wysya proby o uzyskanie lub
to get or send data from your standalone react application. This is the approach
wysanie danych z twojej autonomicznej aplikacji. Takie podejcie poka ci w tym
I will show you in this module and I will show you how to do that.
module, a poka ci, jak to zrobi.